{
    "database": [
        {
            "question": "Bird which is used in twitter logo?",
            "correct_answer": "Larry",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Larry",
                "Humming Bird",
                "Tweety",
                "Baby crow"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one is the smallest ocean in the World?",
            "correct_answer": "Arctic",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Indian",
                "Pacific",
                "Atlantic",
                "Arctic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country gifted the ‘Statue of Liberty’ to USA in 1886?",
            "correct_answer": "France",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "France",
                "Canada",
                "Brazil",
                "England"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In which ocean Bermuda Triangle region is located?",
            "correct_answer": "Atlantic",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Atlantic",
                "Indian",
                "Pacific",
                "Arctic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country is known as the playground of Europe?",
            "correct_answer": "Switzerland",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Austria",
                "Holland",
                "Switzerland",
                "Italy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country is known as the Land of Thunderbolts?",
            "correct_answer": "Bhutan",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "China",
                "Bhutan",
                "Mongolia",
                "Thailand"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country is also known as the Land of Rising Sun?",
            "correct_answer": "Japan",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Japan",
                "Fiji",
                "India",
                "Bhutan"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In which country, white elephant is found?",
            "correct_answer": "Thailand",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "India",
                "Sri Lanka",
                "Thailand",
                "Malaysia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Total number of oceans in the World is",
            "correct_answer": "5",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "3",
                "5",
                "8",
                "7"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many countries were participated as founding member of United Nation?",
            "correct_answer": "51",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "45",
                "50",
                "51",
                "52"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one is the longest continental mountain range in the world?",
            "correct_answer": "Andes",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Himalaya",
                "Andes",
                "Rocky Mountains",
                "Ural Mountains"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country launched the world’s first nationwise 5G mobile network?",
            "correct_answer": "South Korea",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Japan",
                "India",
                "America",
                "South Korea"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What makes a reptile a reptile?",
            "correct_answer": "Egg laying",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Warm blooded",
                "Cold blooded",
                "Non hearing",
                "Egg laying"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Oxygen and ozone are",
            "correct_answer": "Allotropes",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Isobars",
                "Allotropes",
                "Isotopes",
                "Isomers"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who Won 10th Italian open title 2021?",
            "correct_answer": "Rafael Nadal",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Novak Djokovic",
                "Rafael Nadal",
                "Dominic Thiem",
                "Stefanos Tsitsipas"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Waca cricket ground is located in?",
            "correct_answer": "Perth",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Adelaide",
                "Perth",
                "Auckland",
                "Durban"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The term Dolphin Kick is associated with which of the following games?",
            "correct_answer": "Swimming",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Badminton",
                "Football",
                "Swimming",
                "Kick boxing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which athlete scored first position in the London Marathon held on 4th October 2020?",
            "correct_answer": "Shura Kitata",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Eliud Kipchoge",
                "Shura Kitata",
                "Vincent Kipchumba",
                "Sisay Lemma"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "India shared gold medal with which country in the first online Chess Olympiad 2020?",
            "correct_answer": "Russia",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Russia",
                "Pakistan",
                "Nepal",
                "South Korea"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Swimmer from Australia won 4 gold medals at Tokyo Olympics 2020 – 2021?",
            "correct_answer": "Emma McKeon",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kylee McKeown",
                "Emma McKeon",
                "Lisa Carrington",
                "Katie Ledecky"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following trophies is related to Football?",
            "correct_answer": "Merdeka Cup",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Merdeka Cup",
                "Everest Cup",
                "BC Futball Cup",
                "MS Cup"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which technology company has launched a campaign named Make Small Strong?",
            "correct_answer": "Google",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Microsoft",
                "Google",
                "Amazon",
                "Infosys"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "ChatGPT is developed by?",
            "correct_answer": "OpenAI",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "OpenAI",
                "Google",
                "Twitter",
                "Apple"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which European nation first began sustained campaign of exploration?",
            "correct_answer": "Portugal",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "England",
                "Netherlands",
                "France",
                "Portugal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who amongst the following Mauryan rulers did conquer the Deccan?",
            "correct_answer": "Bindusara",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kunala",
                "Bindusara",
                "Chandragupta",
                "Ashoka"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which planet is known as the Watery Planet?",
            "correct_answer": "Earth",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mercury",
                "Jupiter",
                "Mars",
                "Earth"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one among the following four planets is the biggest in size?",
            "correct_answer": "Earth",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mars",
                "Earth",
                "Venus",
                "Mercury"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The period of one revolution of sun around the centre of galaxy is called",
            "correct_answer": "Cosmic year",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Light year",
                "Cosmic year",
                "Parsec",
                "Astronomical year"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following planets is known as Morning Star?",
            "correct_answer": "Mercury",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mercury",
                "Venus",
                "Moon",
                "Jupiter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Full adder is used to",
            "correct_answer": "3 bit addition",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "2 bit addition",
                "3 bit addition",
                "4 bit addition",
                "5 bit addition"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Any number with an exponent of zero is equal to",
            "correct_answer": "One",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Zero",
                "One",
                "Two",
                "Ten"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "FF is a type of game?",
            "correct_answer": "Third person shooter",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Third person shooter",
                "First person shooter",
                "Team shooter",
                "Single shooter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "FF is not available on",
            "correct_answer": "Nokia 1100",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Nokia 1100",
                "Iphone",
                "Android",
                "iOS"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
